const bagOfQuestions = [
  { 
    question: "What city are the Lakers in?",
    answers: ["New York", "Los Angeles", "Mexico City", "Seattle"],
    correctAnswer: "Los Angeles" 
  },
  {
    question: "How many championships does Lebron have?",
    answers: ["2", "3", "0", "19"],
    correctAnswer: "3"
  },
  {
    question: "Who does Lonzo Ball play for?",
    answers: ["Lakers", "Heat", "Bucks", "Mavericks"],
    correctAnswer: "Lakers"
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the coach of the Spurs?",
    answers: ["Mike Malone", "Tim Hardaway", "Greg Popovich", "Luke Walton"],
    correctAnswer: "Greg Popovich"
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the second pick in the 2016 draft?",
    answers: ["Ben Simmons", "Brandon Ingram", "Devin Harris", "Lonzo Ball"],
    correctAnswer: "Brandon Ingram"
  },
  {
    question: "How many teams are in the NBA?",
    answers: ["25", "30", "60", "120"],
    correctAnswer: "30"
  },
  {
    question: "How many games does each team play at home?",
    answers: ["16", "41", "57", "100"],
    correctAnswer: "41"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the best shot in basketball?",
    answers: ["three-pointer", "lay-up", "Lebron whining and crying to the referee", "dunk"],
    correctAnswer: "Lebron whining and crying to the referee"
  },
  {
    question: "How many minutes are in an NBA game?",
    answers: ["100", "60", "30", "48"],
    correctAnswer: "48"
  },
  {
    question: "What team will win the next 3 championships no matter what",
    answers: ["Warriors", "Clippers", "Cavaliers", "Worchestshires"],
    correctAnswer: "Warriors"
  }
]


